We feel it's pretty good and we also offer some good fringe benefits. Really?
我们觉得这很不错，而且我们还提供一些附加福利。真的吗？
Well,we give you a free dinner,so you eat well.
我们为你提供免费的晚餐，所以你会吃的很好。
Right,better than hostel food!
好的，比招待所的食物要好！
We certainly hope so!And we also offer extra pay for working on national hoildays.
我们希望如此！另外在国家法定假日工作，我们还会多付薪水。
Oh,that's a really good perk,isn't it?
这是一笔很好的额外收入，不是吗？
Yes,we think so.And then because of the difficulties of getting public transport,if you're working after 11 o'clock we drive you home.
是的，我们是这么想的。如果你工作到11点以后，由于难以搭上公共交通，我们会开车送你回家。
Oh,that's good to know.
那太好了。
well,we'd certainly be interested in inviting you for an interview,if you're still interested?
我们希望邀请你来面试，如果你还感兴趣的话？
Oh yes,certainly.Could I just also ask what qualities you're looking for?
当然。我能问一下你们有什么要求吗？
Well,for this particular job we want a clear voice,which you obviously do have! Thank.
这份工作需要有一副清楚的嗓音，你肯定合格！-谢谢。
And you must be able to think quickly,you know. Well,i hope i'd...
你还得思维敏捷。我希望我……
So,when could you come in for an interview? We're actually quite quiet tonight?
那么你什么时候可以来面试？其实我们今晚这里比较安静。
Sorry,I couldn't come tonight.Or tomorrow,I'm afraid.Thursday's okay that'd be 22nd of October. Fine,after 5 p.m.?
对不起，我今晚不能去。恐怕得明天。周四可以，也就是10月22日。好的，晚上5点以后？
Yes,fine.Would 6 o'clock be okay?
可以，6点行吗？
Perfect.And could you bring along the names of two referees?
好极了。你能告诉我两名推荐人的名字吗？
Yes,that's fine,no problem.
好的，没问题。
Good,I look forward to seeing you.
很好，期待与你见面。
Oh,by the way,who should i ask for?
顺便说一下，我应该找谁呢？
Oh yes ,of course,sorry.My name is Samira Manuja.
是的，对不起。我叫莎米拉·马努扎。
Can you spell that,please? M-A-N-U-J-A.
请问你能拼一下吗？M-A-N-U-J-A。
Okay.i've got that.Thanks very much.
好的，我记下了。非常感谢。
Look forward to seeing you...
期望在不久之后与你见面……